We have a Russian school at night Well, I almost also
у нас ночь Ну у меня почти тоже света
have no light, but this kid What is the word of
нет а вот этот пацан Что кричит слово
Russia shouting Let him say What is the glory of
России Пусть он скажет А в чем слава
Russia,
России
consider it just a SLR,
это считай так сказать просто зеркалка
I can say what is the Glory of Ukraine what is the
я могу сказать в чем Слава Украине в чем
glory of
слава России
Russia what is the Glory of Ukraine Ukraine  a free
в чем Слава Украине Украина свободная
country, for example, What is the glory of
страна например А в чем слава России
Russia? Come on, I can take,
я Давай так я могу Ты можешь взять
for example, an empty piece of paper A 4 and go to the
например пустой листочек А 4 и выйти на
square of your city, just stand for 15
площадь своего города просто постоять 15
minutes with an empty piece of paper, you
минут пустым листочку можешь
can just go out and see,
вот просто я выйду посмотрим
I won’t be shorter, it will be filmed
я не буду короче будет снимать в прямом
live Like a dude  the city center came out with a white
эфире Как чувак вышел центр города белым
sheet And you will go out Well, maybe
листом И ты выйдешь Ну может быть
you can at least be a journalist, well, come on like this And
журналиста можете хотя бы ну давай так А
if you go out with an A4 sheet And it
если ты выйдешь вот с листочком А4 И там
will say the glory of Russia, let's not the
будет написано слава России давай не
owl of Russia, this is our enemy, yes But
сова России это это враг наш да А вот
just with a white sheet, this is not
просто с белым листом это никакие не
slogan Here, let me go out with white and you
лозун Вот давай я выйду с белым и ты
made the same white sheets
сделал одинаковые белые листы
I can’t do anything let
мне ничего нельзя делать попробуем
’s try here I am from the city of Khmelnitsky What city
вот я из города Хмельницкий Ты из какого
Khmelnitsky are you from which city
Хмельницкий Ты из какого города
on the square  Ohschad And you are in St. George's
на площадь А ты в георгиевском Завтра
Tomorrow, really, tomorrow at 10:00 am we go out
вот реально завтра в 10:00 утра выходим
and do a
и делаем
planned exercise at 10 am, you go
10 утра планового учения
out with a blank sheet to the city
выходишь пустым листом к городской
administration for 15 minutes
администрации 15 минут
Yes, write telegrams
Да телеграм напиши
that tomorrow we will go out,
что завтра будем выходить
we will go out super that the phone is
будем выходить супер то что телефон
how I live there
как я там живут
Nikolay My name is Nikolay
Николай Меня зовут Николай
I’ll write down Nikolai’s phone, damn it, I really
запишу телефон Николая блин реально
found a free Russian, it’s cool, it’s
нашел свободного русского это круто это
cool, but I can write, for example,
круто а я могу типа написать например
now an announcement that Tomorrow there will be
сейчас анонс что Завтра вот будет
such an action in Femitsk and Georgievsk that,
фемицком и Георгиевске такая акция что
like a Russian Ukrainian, they will prove to each other
типа русский украинец докажут друг другу
that they have free states,
что у них свободные государства
there’s nothing, nothing will happen, you
нет ничего не будет тебе ничего не
won’t be
будете
naked  you don’t have an
голая жопы нет
ass you can walk with a bare ass you can walk with a
у вас можно ходить с голой жопой можно
disappeared ass even a white sheet In short
исчезлой жопой хоть белым листком Короче
you won’t go out
не выйдешь
yes yes I understand that your carpets and carpets are
да да понял то и ковры и ковры у вас
cooler than ours yes
круче чем у нас да
carpet
ковер
And how do you clean it by the way I
А вы как его чистите кстати ковер
understand the carpet
понял
shorter telephone I wrote down your
короче телефончик я твои записал завтра
contact in the morning  so man The three of
контактируем утром так мужик Мы втроем
us live without anyone without parents
сами живем без кого-либо без родителей
and you will tell me what kind of carpet I am
и ты мне будешь говорить что я за ковер
and he is  o
а он именно
like it
нравится
You were looking for an apartment with a carpet, that is, like, I
Вы искали квартиру с ковром то есть типа
’m looking for a type from realtors I want an apartment with a
ищу типа у риэлторы Я хочу квартиру с
carpet like this, agreed it was
ковром типа такие договорились он тут
already hanging here Hello Have you looked
уже висел Алло А вы заглядывали что там
behind the carpet Maybe there is something there Secret
за ковром Может там что-то есть Тайный
passage bookmark with mephedrone
ход закладка с мефедроном
Do you yourself live without  girls,
А вы сами живете без девчонок
look Let's go further, what else is the glory of
посмотри Давай дальше в чем еще слава
Russia,
России
too, Russia Freedom So what is the glory of
тоже Россия Свобода Так в чем слава
Russia, unlike you, you are independent, you depend
в отличие от Вас независим вы зависите
on Iran, for example,
от Ирана например
some pancake Iran delivers you pancake drones
вам какой-то блин Иран вам блин дроны
Putin flew Iran
поставляет Путин летал Иран для того
to bow to this pancake podishah
чтобы кланялся этому блин подишаху
Iranian for that  that give us drones
иранскому для то что дай нам дроны
geranium
герань
mess
бардак
Yes, we are so cool you understand Look
Да мы настолько крутые понимаешь Смотри
now I'm explaining to you
сейчас я тебе объясняю
Listen Listen bro Look you
Послушай Послушай братан Смотри ты
look We are given for free You know why
смотри Нам дают бесплатно Знаешь почему
Because three bayraktar that they give us
Потому что три байрактар что нам дают
bayraktar because we
байрактар потому что мы реклама
show ads look how the old
показывают смотри как старом расфигачили
Russian was blown up Oh everyone buys and so  next
русский О все покупают и так далее
Let's tell me what's in your room
Давай скажи вот что у тебя в комнате
made in Russia your phone is
сделано в России телефон у тебя
Russian
российский
so independent you can see on the computer
так независимые видно дальше компьютеры
you have a Russian
у тебя российский
[music]
[музыка]
computer China
компьютер Китай
Well, no soon there will be no Independent And
Ну нет скоро будет нету Независимый А
what kind of car will there be At
какая будет машина Какая
least one Ukrainian car industry is
хотя бы одну украинский автопром это
the same
такой же
post-Soviet [ __ ] as you are the Russian
постсоветское [__] как и вас российский
car industry What AvtoVAZ Look at you are telling
автопром Что АвтоВАЗ Смотри ты мне тут
me no Tell me
говоришь нет Вот скажи
that I am in the room at all  besides the carpet,
что я в комнате вообще кроме ковра
let me ask you now what is in
давайте сейчас спрошу у тебя что у тебя
your hut on No, you say there you are
в хате на Не ну вы говорите там вы
Independent or something That's all there, you
Независимый что ли Вот там все вот вы вы
depend stupidly on everyone with all your goods,
всеми товарами зависите тупо от всех у
you have nothing but a carpet Russian
вас ничего кроме ковра нету российской
that you Let's spin the three of you,
что вас Давай покрутите вас трое
spin them with bread rolls  on the sides
покрутить их хлебальниками по сторонам
say that you have a Russian
скажите что у вас Российская
sense that Russian
смысле что Российская
Listen to you in Ukraine, let's do everything You
Слушай у вас в Украине давай всё Ты
merged
слился
you merged with you except
ты слился у тебя кроме
Georgievsky Here, apart from the carpet and the three of
Георгиевский Вот кроме ковра и вас трех
you, they made three of you in Russia, the carpet was made
вас сделали трех в России ковер сделали
in Russia that the bedside table is
в России что и тумбочка вот это
antediluvian that besides the three of you  dodikov
допотопная что кроме вас трех додиков
carpet bedside tables was made in Russia
тумбочки ковра было сделано в России
what in your what in your this apartment
что в вашем что вашей этой квартире
besides you three houses of the
кроме вас трех домиков
carpet bedside table
тумбочки ковра сделано
what was done besides you
то что кроме вас
in
сделана в России
Russia you haven’t done anything in Russia
у тебя ничего не сделано в России
what’s in this Russian room say
что в этой комнате российского скажи
come on Come on here in this apartment
давай Ну давай вот в этой квартире
furniture [ __ ]
мебель [__]
energy is
энергия
not from the goods that’s what you
не вот из товара вот что у вас
get furniture that is Show furniture
получается мебель то есть Покажи мебель
Show what Russian furniture is
Покажи Какую мебель российской
shorter old furniture fittings furniture
короче старая мебель фурнитура мебели
fittings  it’s definitely not Russian
фурнитура точно не Российская
toilets that you don’t have in any way
унитазы у вас по-любому нету
Where did you get the toilets from which company the toilet is
Откуда вас унитазы унитаз какой фирмы
I don’t know if you have it
Я не знаю у вас Значит
So you don’t have a toilet I caught
у тебя нет унитаза я поймал
such carpets you didn’t have toilets
такими коврами унитазов не было не было
if you say that you have a
если ты говоришь что у тебя унитаз
Russian toilet what company Which Russian
российский какой фирмы Какая Российская
Yes  you tell me how old you are Lord 41
Да ты скажи сколько тебе лет Господи 41
years old to wild In short, I’m not ashamed more than
год до дикий Короче не стыдно больше чем
you in total 2 so I’m not ashamed at all I
вам в сумме 2 так вот вообще не стыдно Я
’m waiting I’m happy I found free
жду Я счастливый Я нашел свободных
independent Russians who don’t depend
независимых русских которые не зависят
on any Russian things at all
вообще от никаких русских вещей Смотри
Xiaomi Huawei Yes, she hasn’t been Russian for a long time.
фирма Xiaomi Huawei Да она давно себя не
just you say that you are like
просто вы говорите что вы типа
independent, so it turns out And what do you
независимые так то получается А что вы
produce that
производите что
we are not dependent who told you this, otherwise
мы не зависимый кто тебе это сказал а то
you are dependent
вы зависимы
then Russia is a dependent country
то Россия зависимая страна
and you are directly independent I just say Russia is
а Вы прям независи Я просто скажи Россия
dependent or independent
зависимая или независимая
Ukraine does not depend on anyone but look
Украина ни от кого не зависит да смотри
Russia  then Russia, I understand you recognized that
Россия то Россия я понял вы признали что
Russia is dependent Yes, you understand what
Россия зависимая Да ты понимаешь что
independence is in principle,
такое в принципе независимость
come on, let's summarize you poor
давай так давай подрезюмируем вас бедная
country, you have nothing Russian
страна у вас российского ничего нету
except carpets and bedside tables
кроме коврах и тумбочки
, you have nothing Russian in your room,
у вас в комнате вот из ваших вещей
really, because
российского ничего нет правда потому что
Russian This is [ __ ]  you buy phones that are
Российская Это [__] вы телефоны
not Russian Yes, the computer is not
покупаете не российские Да комп не
Russian teapot is not a Russian iron Not
российские чайник не российский утюг Не
Russia
России
with you Come with me,
с тобой Давай со мной
in principle, the food industry is all
в принципе пищевая промышленность вся
ours, what yours
наша какой ваша
look like Russian
смотришь российское
Are you what are you Russian food
Ты что ну что ты российский продукты
Russian you eat
российский ты кушаешь
everything the same that, for example, you can
все то же самое что например можешь
eat Well, tell me  tell me Name the foods
съесть Ну скажи скажи Назови продукты
you eat Are you crazy or
которыми ты питаешься Ты что [__]
what is her name today  schnim
что ли ведь она звать сегодняшним
breakfast [ __ ] yes yes Well, so I put
завтрак [__] да да Ну чтобы я поставил
A borscht I have hawal cutlets hawal mashed potatoes in the morning
А борщ Я с утра хавал котлет хавал пюре
So I also
Так что еще
drank coffee I don’t drink I don’t like
кофе пил кофе Не пью я не люблю
sense in Russia I
смысл в России
buy Well, yes
покупаю Ну да
Where do you grow beets in gardens
Где у вас выращивается свеклу в огородах
in gardens do you grow beets in your garden
в огородах ты в огороде выращиваешь
you buy in the store
свеклу или ты в магазине покупаешь
I go to the fair I buy homemade
я хожу на ярмарке покупаю домашнюю
beets And I clearly understood Everything I understood yes yes
свеклу А понял явно Все все понял да да
So you have more like beetroot
Значит у тебя больше типа свекольный
such yes well done
такой да молодец
salt where you buy
соль где покупаешь
there is no light
нету света
will go soon or now I’m already in the bunker
вскоре пойдет или сейчас я уже в бункере
that you don’t see the dude is
что чувак не видишь
flying and you are flying  all those examples
летает и у вас летают все те примеры
that you gave me about the phone and there
которые ты мне привел про телефон и там
about technology This is business this is market relations this is
про технику Это бизнес это рыночные это
market relations Let's
рыночные отношения Давайте под
sum it up, let's boys,
подрезюмирую давайте пацаны
let's say that we didn't quarrel,
давайте что мы не ссорились вот просто
just summarize and
под резюмируем и Разведемся резюмируем
get divorced, we'll summarize you build young guys live In
вы строим молодых парней живете В
forgetting this hut of money, nothing
забывчиной этой хате денег ничего
Russian except  carpet In the bedside table and
российского кроме ковра В тумбочке и
also the bedside tables, the fittings are not all
тоже тумбочки фурнитура вся не
Russian yes Because if we
Российская да Потому что если мы будем
disassemble So they are left after the Soviet
разбирать Так что они после Советского
Union  axis pancake in fact live on the
Союза осталось блин по сути живёте на
Legacy of the Soviet
Наследие Советского Союза
Union you have a carpet of the Soviet Union with a bedside table of the
у тебя ковёр Советского Союза с тумбочка
Soviet Soviet Union
Советского Советского Союза
look again what that Russia
посмотри ещё раз что что Россия
built after the Soviet Union let's
построила после Советского Союза давай
hydroelectric power station what
гидроэлектростан какую
hydroelectric power station you built after the
гидроэлектростанцию вы построили после
Soviet Union dude name the
Советского Союза чувак назвич
Baksan hydroelectric power station where is it from my republic
баксанская ГЭС где это с моей республики
where is it Baksanskaya  in what year it was
где Это баксанская в каком году
built
построена
Yes, I don’t remember Still Under the Soviet Union Yes,
Да не помню Еще При Советском Союзе Да
in the second year Now I’ll look at the
во втором году Сейчас я посмотрю
Baksan state, maybe you really
баксанское государство может реально вы
separated from you and you started
мы от вас отсоединились и вы начали
building something
что-то строить
Baksan hydroelectric power station
баксанская ГЭС
1936 in short, they did it under Stalin
1936 году короче сделали еще при Сталине
1936 Baksan hydroelectric power station
1936 год баксанская ГЭС
What are you  built Look, while we
Ты что вы построили Вот смотри Пока мы
were in the Soviet Union Damn, we
были в Советском Союзе Блин мы вам
built everything for you Yes, as soon as we separated from you,
строили все Да как только мы от вас
what did you build without us,
отделились что вы построили без нас да
what did you build without us, tell me, look,
что вы построили без нас скажи смотри
come on, you don’t have Russian ones When it was
давай у вас российских нет Когда было
Ukraine, we built the Baikal-
Украина мы вам строили в Тюмени Байкал
Amur Mainline in Tyumen  hydroelectric power plants
амурскую магистраль гидроэлектростанции
before our people and specialists were building when
до наши люди и специалисты строили когда
we disconnected  what did you build name
мы отсоединились что вы построили назови
at least one hydro power plant somewhere
хоть один гидро электростанцию куда-то
to build in 30 plus years
станцию чтобы построили за 30 плюс лет
without us
без нас
oh right you built it tell me you
ой прям вы так что построили скажи ты же
started me Tell me what you built in
меня начался Скажи что вы построили в
Russia
России
Yes List at least three things
Да Перечисли Хоть три каких-то вещи
back that independent Russia  built
назад что независимая Россия построила
Let's
Давай
get the phone yes now while the kid yes on the
полез телефон да сейчас пока пацан да в
Internet it
интернет
turns out look we while we were all 15
получается смотри мы пока мы были все 15
republics with you fed Russia built the
республик с вами кормили Россию строили
Crimean bridge Nord Stream 2 look
Крымский мост Северный поток 2 смотри
let's see Yes the Crimean bridge was built
давай Да смотри Крымский мост построили
Okay Nord Stream was built and
Окей Северный поток построили и завод
some kind of plant was built Yes we built power plants
какой-то построили Да электростанции
they are building they are resuming
строят возобновляют
that you have built a new one We are also
что вы построили новое У нас тоже мосты
building bridges Yes, they are also building pipelines
строят Да тоже там трубопроводы строят
there, it’s not something like that right there
еще это же не что-то там такое прям
Supernatural
Сверхъестественное
Come on Where did you build something in short
Давай Где у вас что короче построили А
Well, because when we were there the
ну потому что когда мы были там страны
Baltic countries Latvia Lithuania Estonia Ukraine
балтии Латвия Литва Эстония Украина
Kazakhstan all  built Baikal, the Amur
Казахстан всем строили Байкал амурскую
Mainline, our students went
магистраль наши студенты отправлялись
there, young guys built, and what did you
туда строили молодые парни а вы что без
build without us  What plant in the city what was
нас построили Какой завод в городе что
built in your city during the time of
построено в твоем городе время
Independence of Russia yes When you left
Независимости России да Когда вы вышли
the Soviet Union
из Советского Союза
So you are in your city again in
Так что ты в твоем городе еще раз в
your city what did you build in 30 years
твоем городе что вы за 30 лет построили
Where were you for 30 years
Где вы были 30 лет
parks we make the
парки делаем
whole world makes parks what are you
весь мир делает парки что вы такое
we did it right Wow,
сделали что вот прям Вау
at least we don’t demolish monuments, look
мы памятники хотя бы не сносим смотри
Once again, what did you build in your Georgievsk
Еще раз что вы в своем Георгиевске
yes or no, or are you going to
построили да или нет или идешь нафиг
see
сливаешь
what the population of your village is
сколько населения вашем этом поселке
15,000 look at 15,000 you have an Ice
15000 смотри на 15000 есть у вас Ледовый
Palace
дворец
who has an Ice Palace No well  and what they didn’t
кто Ледовой дворец есть Нет ну а что не
build and what Well, I understood, I
построили а что Хорошо я понял я
swung at a very huge Ice
замахнулся на очень огромной Ледовой
Palace And what did you build that
дворец А что вы построили что
independent Russia built
независимая Россия построила вам
St. Petersburg for you not St. Petersburg in your
Петербург не санкт-петербург вашем
Georgievsk Look when we were with you
Георгиевске Смотри когда мы были с вами
in the Soviet Union, we built factories for you
в Советском Союзе мы вам заводы
now google Georgievsky
построили сейчас нагуглите Георгиевский
so that he
чтобы он построили
how much we built so say that without us you
сколько мы так скажи что ты без нас
built the opera theater in this Georgievsk
построил в этом Георгиевске
Listen, I opened a kid in the cat of this
ёперный театр Слушай я в кошке этого
Georgievsk
Георгиевска открыл
ana I opened the pictures of Georgievsk
пацаны Я открыл фотки Георгиевска
this is a
это
city Name the city
город Назови город
I thought you had something serious there I
Я думал у вас там что-то серьезное я
opened the pictures and looked
открыл фотки и посмотрел
Let me score in Moscow
Пускай забил в Москву санкт-петербург
st.  Near the
теперь встречный вопрос У вас Возле
cinema
кинотеатра
near the city of Dyura, the
дюры
city of
город
Dude, I want to see these pictures of
Чувак я хочу посмотреть эти фотки
Georgievsk 19 places with photos with descriptions
Георгиевска 19 мест фото с описаниями
and there are still such cities right
и существует ещё такие города прямо
in your place, they even made a fountain in the park, yes
у вас даже фонтанчик в парке сделали да
in Ukraine a
в Украине
little more than our city
чуть больше чем наш город
400 thousand people lived,
400 тысяч населения жила
I look at you say you are monuments  don’t
я смотрю по Вы говорите Вы памятники не
take it down, I’m looking at what kind of [ __ ] you have around the
сносите я смотрю какой у вас срач вокруг
monuments, you can’t see anything
памятников неухожена ничего видно
St. George’s plaque-fly
Георгиев бляха-муха
Name your city
Назови свой город
I’ve been talking to you so far I thought it’s a
Я пока с вами говорил Я думал там
serious city And now, in short, stupidly
серьезный город А сейчас короче тупо
I’ve come in looking at pictures of this Georgievsk
зашел смотрю фотки этого Георгиевска
You’re
Ты специально
specially looking Here, take it on Google, open
я смотрю Вот возьми в Google открой
St. George’s pictures  it’s just shorter there
Георгиевский картинки там просто короче
You’re better Listen to the
Ты лучше Слушай мужичок
little man st. petersburg  tr Aurora Yes, it’s like it is a
кинотеатр Аврора Да он как есть есть
cinema The new Aurora cinema was built
кинотеатр Новый построили кинотеатр
that it
Аврора что он такой убитый
didn’t like it so dead It’s why it really
не понравился Он почему вот реально
grows
растет
We have
У нас
really
реально
I’m shorter
я короче
it’s just an obedient city
это просто послушно город
five years
там и тут траву не выдирали лет пять
yes
да
And she has a new look you
И у нее есть новое смотрите вас
built a shopping center Russia there is
построили торговый центр Россия есть
such
такой
there is such a landscape design near it
есть есть возле него такой ландшафтный
just damn it really I
дизайн просто блин реально я такого
haven’t seen anything like this anywhere else this is really a
нигде еще не видел это вот это реально
test I don’t joke around in front of this
зачет я не стебут вокруг перед этим
shopping center Russia is very all ear is
торговым центром Россия очень все ухо
good
хорошо
Damn, and even go nuts And once again
Блин да еще [__] А еще раз наркоманов
there are a lot of drug addicts, I see it wrong
много не так я вижу
Name your city I called it like at the
Назови свой город Я называл типа еще в
very beginning
самом начале
I opened another photo of this cinema from a
я другую другую фотку этого кинотеатр
different angle there are these
другого ракурса открыл там еще эти
square teplites still Svetki really
теплиты квадратные еще Светки реально
here we had such a reinforced concrete plant it was
вот у нас завод был такой железобетонный
teplit these  grass sticks out of them.
он теплиты эти из них трава торчит
Well, the USSR, in fact, but wait, I’m
Ну СССР по факту но подожди-подлинение я
just looking at how you have developed in 30 years
просто смотрю как вы развились за 30 лет
without us with us to  when Ukraine was with
без нас при нас когда Украина была с
you in the USSR it was a normal city it was a
вами в СССР нормальный был город
normal modern city for 30 years you
нормальный современный за 30 лет вы даже
can’t even get grass Near the cinema it’s shorter
траву не можете Возле кинотеатра короче
yo-my It’s awesome In short, okay guys,
ё-моё Это [__] Короче ладно пацаны
look I’m just already tight with you
смотрите Я просто уже с вас только
that In short, I already don’t have the strength to
поджал что Короче у меня уже сил нету
wait so much, I understand, in short, let’s
столько ждать я понял короче давайте
cut you 3 to there who live in the
подрез вы 3 до там которые живут в
city of Georgievsk, who from
городе Георгиевск у которых из
Russian have only a carpet
российского есть только ковёр
bedside table
тумбочка
Russian live in  really cool
Российская живете в реально крутых
conditions and how the interior When you
условиях и как интерьер Когда вы
go out, I understand at first when
выходите я понимаю я сначала когда с
I talked to you I didn’t understand Why I
вами говорил Я не понимал Почему я Если
If I walked along such streets as I
бы я ходил по таким улицам как я вот
saw in Georgievsk, you will also
увидел в Георгиевске тоже вы будете
Look, I trolled you a little at first
Смотри я сначала троллил вас немножко
because I thought the pancake hung
потому что я думал блин зависла
stuck
зависло